<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="13"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[Flybrid Power 200


    Energy Stored. Emissions Reduced.]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[johnfhuntpower.co.uk]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[Contents















         2                                         3                                          5






          Introduction                             Evolution in                               How does
                                                   Power Supply                               it work?













         6                                         8                                          10






         What are                                  Locations                                  Links

         the results                               & Contacts]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[Introduction






































         Operating from five depots across the UK, we provide a

         truly nationwide service 24 hours per day, 365 days a year.






         High specification, contemporary generators from 20 kVA to 1250 kVA, offer uninterrupted
         power, compliant with the latest environmental, noise and emissions regulations, direct to your
         site whenever you need it.

         Continued investment in the latest temporary power equipment, allows us to offer our clients the
         most efficient and innovative equipment on the market, helping to reduce carbon emissions and
         environmental impact.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[Evolution in Power Supply






































         With rising fuel costs and increased focus on all industries

         to reduce their carbon footprint, we’ve recently introduced
         FLYBRID units to our fleet of temporary power equipment.








         This latest offering will allow our clients to simultaneously reduce their fuel usage, whilst lowering
         the environmental impact of their power supply.


         By using our Flybrid 200 units in conjunction with our diesel generators, we’re able to offer a new
         solution which allows for considerable generator downsizing in many applications.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[Evolution in Power Supply









         Historically, generators have been sized to suit the peak, start-up load demand when used in
         applications such as:

         •       Tower Cranes
         •       Pumps
         •       Hoists
         •       Medical Scanners etc

         With loads of this nature, which have a substantial demand for power on start-up, generators are
         often left to run at low load factors, for long periods of time, resulting in poor fuel economy and
         engine performance.



         Now, by using our Flybrid units, generators can be
         downsized to provide more economical running after
         start-up, reduced fuel usage and much improved
         carbon credentials.]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[How does it work?







































         Flybrid units, contain cutting edge, flywheel energy storage technology and deliver an ultra-fast
         power injection for smooth and controlled generator loading.

         On start-up, when the requirement for load is significantly higher, both generator and Flybrid unit
         work in conjunction to provide the required power.

         Once the demand drops off, the generator runs as a standalone unit and the Flybrid regenerates
         in preparation for the next peak requirement.]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[What are the results?







































         What are the results?






         We have carried out significant testing across a number of major projects, assessing the product
         on live applications across different sectors.


         Amongst our testing, we applied a Flybrid unit to a tower crane set up for a major construction
         client in the Midlands.


         A 300 kVA generator would usually be required to power the crane in question, however, we
         supplied a 150 kVA set and Flybrid unit with great success.]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[What are the results?









         The client experienced the same reliable power supply whilst benefiting from a considerably
         reduced fuel consumption and environmental impact.

         Fuel saving estimation:





                                                                                     Approximate fuel used in a
                 Generator Supplied             Approximate Fuel Consumption
                                                                                       50 Hour Working Week

                      300 kVA                   32 litres per hour @ 50% load                  1,600


                      160kVA                    20 litres per hour @ 50% load                  1,000





         In this example, 600 litres of fuel saved per week represented a vast commercial advantage for
         our client.

         Together with the environmental benefits associated with a drastic reduction in fuel usage, our
         Flybrid package provided the perfect solution for our client’s project.






                Approx Weekly Fuel                    CO  Saving Per Litre              Potential Weekly CO
                                                                                                           2
                       Saving                            2                                   Reduction

                     600 Litres                             2.64 kg                        1.5 TONNES]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Call Us Today









         Protecting our future




         Our aim is to help all businesses achieve their sustainability targets and help to protect our future.
         That’s why we are dedicated to bringing you the cleanest generators for every business need.

         Call our experienced Sales team today and start to see the benefits of using John F Hunt Flybrid
         Generators.



         South East Depot                                            North East Depot

         Magnet Road                                                 Shadon Way
         Grays, Essex                                                Gateshead
         RM20 4DB                                                    DH3 2RN
         01375 366766                                                0191 411 1200

         Midlands Depot                                              Scotland Depot


         Fairfield Park                                              Nasmyth Square
         Halesowen                                                   Livingston
         West Midlands                                               EH54 5GG
         B62 9JL                                                     01506 353399
         0121 559 1818


         South West Depot

         Bradley Road
         Bristol
         BS20 7NZ
         0117 901 2199]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[John F Hunt Power Locations]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[Need more info... see below
























                Power Brochure                     GreenD+ HVO Fuel Brochure             Stage V Brochure



























               Managed Services Brochure           Spec Sheets                           John F Hunt Power Website










                                                johnfhuntpower.co.uk]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[John F Hunt Group


























                                           johnfhunt.co.uk    01375 366700
                                                info@johnfhunt.co.uk
                                     John F Hunt, London Rd, Grays RM20 4DB]]></page></pages></Search>